

ILLUSTRATION & DESIGN

WWW.KIMESTOESTA.COM KIMESTOESTA@GMAIL.COM 407.580.0288

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROFICIENT IN:

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign Adobe Premier Pro Videography Event Planning

WORKING KNOWLEDGE:

Adobe AfterEffects
HTML/CSS
UI/UX
Book Making
Screen Printing
3-D Modeling & Printing
Maya

RECOGNITION

UNIVERSITY SCHOLARS PROGRAM University of Florida | 2015 – 2016

Worked on a University Research Project with Professor Brian Slawson combining design to create an interactive video game to revive Native American Culture and Language.

LEADERSHIP

FILIPINO STUDENT ASSOCIATION

Multimedia Chair | 2013

Directed, filmed, and edited videos to promote FSA events and meetings.

Vice President of Internal Affairs | 2014

Part of the Executive Board, responsible for directing Def Talent Jam Dance Competition, and conducting FSA elections.

EDUCATION

MAY 2016 University of Florida | Gainesville, FL

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

Selected by portfolio review to work in a studio environment that promotes community, collaboration and concept development.

RELEVANT COURSEWORK - VIDEO & ANIMATION

Created work with industry standard cameras for film making and computer generated graphics using Maya, Nuke, and Final Cut Pro.

EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2016 - PRESENT GitHub | San Francisco, CA

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Designed and collborated on cross discipline campaigns for the GitHub marketing. Created event design branding for GitHub Constellation and Git Merge 2017-2018.

MAY 2016 - SEPT 2016 Primal Screen | Atlanta, GA

- SEPI 2016 DESIGN INTERN

Developed digital and interactive media for broadcast, web, mobile, and educational games for clients like PBS, Cartoon Network, and Sesame Street.

AUG 2015 - APRII 2016 University of Florida RecSports | Gainesville, FL MARKETING DEPARTMENT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Designed and collaborated with an internal team of six to create promotional posters, flyers, shirts, and digital ads/videos for the department of Recreational Sports at the University of Florida.

JUNE 2015 - AUG 2015 Yahoo | New York, NY

CREATIVE DEPARTMENT DESIGN INTERN

Designed and assisted with various company brand campaigns including takeover ads for the "For Mobile" campaign and event designs for the press release of the app Yahoo LiveText.

AUG 2014 - MAY 2015 **StarterSpace** | Gainesville, FL

CREATIVE DIRECTOR

Managed design projects and consulted for startup companies within Starterspace. Conceived and designed logos, websites, flyers, and other digital and print material for startups.

MAY 2014 - JULY 2014

 $\textbf{HaulBox Startup Company} \mid \textit{Gainesville, FL}$

BRAND IDENTITY DESIGNER

Conceptualized and designed brand identity including logo, icons, and app interface for the startup company HaulBox.